呦 趕緊!
Yo,hurry up!
別落下我
Don't start without me.
快滾過來 快點
Move your ass. Come on.
我TM在給你拿啤酒呢 住嘴!
I'm gettin' your damn beer. Shut up!
你住嘴 賤人 住嘴?
Shut up,woman. Shut up?
哦 要我住嘴 啊?
Oh,me shut up,huh?
都給我住嘴
Shut up,everyone.
Will 是你嗎?
Will,is that you?
Will? 好戲上演了
Will? Here he comes.
Will?
他倒下了
He's down.
來啊 站起來 站起來
Go on,get up. Get up.
別幹傻事哦
Don't be stupid.
我們不想惹麻煩
We don't want any trouble.
要什麼就自己拿吧
Take whatever you want.
我才不管你要怎麼樣
I don't care what you want.
你沒有理由傷害她們啊
There's no reason to hurt anyone.
又是一腳
Here it comes.
一定疼死了
That had to hurt.
你丫怎麼可能... 知道我有什麼理由?
How could you possibly... Know what my reasons are?
這傢伙想站起來
Our boy's trying to get up.
哪個是你的妞兒?
Which one of them belongs to you?
我猜猜
Let me guess.
哦 求求你別傷害他! 求求你
Oh,please don't hurt him! Please.
就是她了
It could be her.
和你丈夫吻別吧
Kiss your husband goodbye.
William...
你們為什麼要這麼做? 為什麼?
Why are you doing this? Why?
為什麼不呢?
Why not?
拍到了嗎? 拍到了 兄弟
Did you get that? I got it,baby.
有多少死者?
And how many dead?
好的 好 我們會盡快過去的 謝謝
Ok. Yeah,we'll be there as soon as we can. Thanks.
得掛了 讓我猜猜
Well,i gotta go. Let me guess.
別想早下班了 入室行兇 四人死亡
Don't get comfortable. We've got 4 dead in a home invasion.
要去哪? 就在本地 華盛頓東南部
Where we headed? It's local. Southeast d.c.
死因是什麼? 鈍器造成的外傷 未使用刀具和槍支
What was the cause of death? Blunt force trauma. No knife,no gun.
要求我們介入嗎? 是的 警方希望我們去現場和他們碰頭
Have we been invited in? Yeah. Cops want us to meet them at the crime scene.
東南部不是最近打砸搶很猖獗嗎?
Isn't southeast where all that vandalism's been lately?
對 就是那一區域 覺得其中有聯繫嗎?
Same area,yeah. Think they could be connected?
不知道 但使用的兇器與 典型入室行兇手法並不相符
I don't know. I mean,the weapon doesn't exactly fit the typical m.o.of a home invasion killer.
倒是值得考慮
Well, it's worth considering.
打砸搶升級到命案很常見
It's common for vandalism to escalate into violence.
加上很多人都有怒氣 該街區的居民大部分都是工薪階層的黑人
Plus there's a lot of anger out there. That neighborhood's mostly black working class.
是的 現在要改造成高級社區  那堛漫~民日子就更難過了
Yeah. Now it's being gentrified while the people who live there are having a tough time.
受害人很有錢? 嗯 是兩對夫婦
Were the victims wealthy? Yeah,it was two couples.
都是新搬過去的有錢人家
The were both part of the influx of new wealth in the area.
有東西被搶嗎? 什麼都沒拿
Police report a robbery? Nothing was taken.
受害人什麼種族?
What race were the victims?
一對是白人 一對是黑人
One couple was white, the other black.
動機不是種族仇恨
Not racially motivated.
JJ 通知Rossi和Reid 我們五點出發
Jj,find rossi and reid, tell them we leave in 5.
如果這和打砸搶有所關聯  殺死四人 可是相當猛烈的升級啊
Well,if this is related to vandalism, 4 dead is a hell of an escalation.
這麼說有可能還會死更多?
So there's the potential for a lot more bodies out there?
這正是我擔心的
That's what i'm afraid of.
犯罪心理 第五季 第04集 絕望
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode04 Hopeless
Kingman Brewster Jr. 說過 (美國教育學家外交家 曾任耶魯校長)
Kingman brewster jr.Said,
"暴力無法給人持久的希望 只能讓人暫不心絕"
"there is no lasting hope in violence, only temporary relief from hopelessness."
Andrews探員? 我是Jennifer Jareau
Detective andrews? Jennifer jareau.
這是探員Rossi Morgan Hotchner  Prentiss和Reid博士
These are agents rossi, morgan, hotchner,prentiss, and dr. Reid.
謝謝你們這麼快趕過來 你有什麼消息?
Thanks for getting here so fast. What can you tell us?
看起來一名受害人是下車時遭到攻擊的
Looks like one of the victims was attacked when he got out of his car.
兇手很可能用他的鑰匙開了門 讓其他受害者大吃一驚
Meaning whoever did this probably used his keys to get inside and surprise the other victims.
是誰發現屍體的?
Who found the bodies?
清潔工 她正在錄口供
The cleaning woman. She's giving her statement now.
Dave 你和Morgan還有Prentiss進去看看 我們負責這兒
Dave,would you,morgan, and prentiss go inside. We'll cover out here.
我知道你們對這種案子都習慣了 不過 堶扈u是慘不忍睹
I know you're all used to this, but,uh,it's a hell of a sight in there.
下得了這樣的手 連畜生都不如
Whoever did this ain't human.
鄰居看到了什麼嗎?
The neighbors see anything?
你們也知道 因為打砸搶行為太多 該區的巡邏車數量都加倍了 卻沒什麼線索
Oh,you know, the patrol cars are even doubled in this area because of t vandalismNothing.
不明嫌犯的行動肯定非常迅速有效
The unsub would have to be extremely fast and efficient.
看這個 這有一大灘血  受害人被拖到門口 沿途有滴狀血跡
Look at this. There's a pool of blood here and then drops as the victim moves toward the door.
受害人什麼身材? 1米85到1米88吧 怎麼了?
How big was the victim? 6'1",6'2". Why?
如果他能自己走過去的話  應該會有搏鬥的痕跡
Well,if he was strong enough to move under his own power, you'd expect signs of a struggle.
如果沒有 也應會有被拽動的痕跡
And if not,there'd most likely be drag marks.
他是被抬過去的
He was carried.
一個人抬他可是很沉的
That's a lot of dead weight for one person to move alone.
門廊處也沒有大灘血跡
There's no pool of blood on the porch,
說明兇手不需要把他放下來 再去開門
which means they didn't have to set him down to open the door.
受害人甲被放在了這
Victim one gets dropped here.
同時受害人乙走到了拐角看出了什麼事...
While number 2 comes around the corner to see what's happening, and...
不明嫌犯在這襲擊了他
The unsub attacks him here.
第一次襲擊時 女性受害人也許還坐在桌邊
The female victims were probably here when the first attack occurred.
也就是說 得有人能馬上控制住她們
Which means somebody would have to control them pretty quickly.
你覺得有幾個不明嫌犯?
How many unsubs are you thinking?
至少得有一個把屍體搬進來 另一個襲擊受害人乙
At least one to move the body inside, another one to take out man number 2,
再來一個控制住其他兩個
And one more to subdue the others.
打砸搶可是會滋生從眾心理的
Well,vandalism breeds a pack mentality.
如果是同一夥人的話  我們找的就是三到四人的團體
If it is the same unsubs, we're looking at a group of 3,maybe 4.
肯定不是未成年人 他們的行動太有效了
These aren't kids. They're too efficient.
局面控制精準 青少年沒那麼縝密
There's a control and precision. Juveniles are sloppy.
我同意 這些手法都很嫻熟
He's right. There is nothing tentative about these kills.
沒有任何新手的痕跡
There's no experimentation.
這些人知道自己在幹什麼
These guys know what they're doing.
我不確定 你有什麼想法?
I don't know. What are you thinking?
我能理解打砸搶升級成命案 但那也是逐漸演變的
I can understand vandalism escalating into violence, but that's usually gradual.
比如先襲擊或謀殺一個人 可這個?
And assault, a single murder maybe, but come on,this?
一夜之間就進化完全了
This feels fully evolved.
9月3日 15輛豪華轎車的窗玻璃被打碎
September 3rd, 15 luxury cars had their windows smashed.
9月14日 一家新開的高級精品服裝店遭搶
September 14th, a new upscale clothing boutique was vandalized.
9月24日 兩家以富人為主顧的餐館遭襲擊
September 24th, two different restaurants, both catering to a wealthy clientele,
正面窗戶被打碎 店內財物被破壞
had their front windows smashed and their interiors torn apart,
最後是10月1日
and finally,october 1st,
一戶新裝修的人家在搬進去前被徹底洗劫
a newly renovated townhome was ransacked before the family could move in.
這麼說他們攻擊的目標從公共財物變成了 私人住所 但是沒有受害人
So they went from attacking public property to a private residence, but no victim.
問題是 是什麼讓他們從那樣... 變成了這樣?
The question is,what makes them move from that... To this?
打砸搶的地點 都代表著這個街區 快速演變的外在和經濟狀況
The vandalism targets were all symbols of the neighborhood's changing makeup and economy.
而這些受害人 也許有什麼特別的地方激怒了不明嫌犯
Maybe there's something specific about these victims that set the unsubs off.
我已經和他們的家人談過了
I've spoken to the victims' family members.
他們答應盡力協助我們調查
They've agreed to come in and help however they can.
Garcia 查查幾個社交網站
Garcia,check social networking sites.
看看不明嫌犯有沒有在網上策劃襲擊
See if these unsubs have coordinated these attacks online.
就算只吱過一聲 我也會像獵狗一樣 把他們揪出來 長官
If they dare tweet, I shall flush them out like a bird dog,sir.
有一個疑問 為什麼不明嫌犯 在社區堹鄐ㄓ牏H注意呢?
We need to be asking how these unsubs manage to not stand out in this neighborhood.
這些犯罪地點 都是新興財富和地位的象徵
Each of these crime scene locations are a representation of new wealth and status,
但它們的周圍區域 仍是長期的住戶
but the area surrounding the crime scenes are still populated by longtime residents
他們逐漸遭到排擠
who are slowly being pushed out.
許多被排擠的人 都為社區的翻新出過力
That's a lot of disenfranchised people who are all part of the neighborhood makeup.
不明嫌犯不招人注意 極有可能是因為他們就住在這
Most likely these unsubs don't stand out because they're probably local themselves.
我不覺得 我同意Rossi的推測
I don't know. I'm with rossi.
我是說 他們很憤怒我能理解  可如此的狠手?
I mean,anger I get, but this much violence?
兇手至少是三個滿腔憤怒的人
We're looking at at least 3 men with an incredible amount of rage.
這種情緒怎麼藏的住?
Where do you hide that?
Turner
Turner.
能不能告訴這位女士 已經10月14日了 她怎麼還不能搬進新房子?
You care to tell the lady why it's october 14th and she's still not ready to move into her house?
可能不行
Not particularly.
你說什麼?
What did you just say?
算了 沒關係的
It's ok. Really.
不 有關係 向這位女士道歉 回答問題
No,it's not. Why don't you apologize to the lady, answer the question.
對不起 女士 我發現地基有點小問題
My apologies,ma'am. Found a slight flaw in the foundation.
我不想你晚上一個人在家時
Hate to think of you home all alone at night,
整棟房子突然塌下來
suddenly the whole place just collapses underneath you.
好了 回去敲石膏板吧 我雇你就是幹這個的
Ok. Now get back to the drywall. That's what I pay you for.
讓別人擔心那地基吧
Let somebody else worry about the foundation.
我讓Garcia查了目標區域的記錄
I had garcia run records on anyone in the target area
看去年有誰的抵押物贖回權被取消的
who in the last year was foreclosed upon, filed for bankruptcy,
申請過破產或失業的 然後把名單縮小到
or applied for unemployment and then narrowed that list down to men
25至45歲的男性 結果呢?
between the ages of 25 and 45. And?
有713個符合
713 hits.
受害人家屬來了
Victims' families are here.
節哀順變
I'm very sorry about your son.
我們想要查清 這到底是模式化行兇 還是隨機案件
We're looking to see if there's a pattern or if your son's killing was truly random.
這麼說 就你知道的 沒有什麼威脅?
So,there were no threats that you knew of?
沒有
No.
我能理解這對你來說不容易
I understand this is very difficult for you.
我們也正盡力查出頭緒
We're just trying to make some sense of it.
請坐
Please.
Barnes女士 你需不需要等會再談?
Ms.Barnes,do you need some more time?
他們說如果我想 可以看看William的屍體
They said I could see william's body if I wanted to.
我覺得那不會有什麼好處的
I don't see what good could come from that.
那你們家就你和你哥哥?
It was just you and your brother?
我們的父母幾年前就過世了
Our parents died a few years ago.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我知道很多人都會這麼說 但是...
I know that sounds like something people say, but...
我是真心的 感到難過
I truly am sorry.
你成天都碰到這樣的案子嗎?
You deal with cases like this all the time.
是的
Yes,i do.
那對你就是家常便飯了
So it's routine for you.
這種事不會有家常便飯的 Barnes女士
There's nothing routine about what you're going through,ms. Barnes.
你有兄弟姐妹嗎?
Do you have brothers and sisters?
有兩個姐妹
I have two sisters.
如果她們發生了這種事你會怎麼做?
What would you do if something like this happened to one of them?
我會竭盡一切抓到兇手
I would do everything in my power to catch the people who did it.
Will? 是你嗎? Will?
Will? Is that you? Will?
來看這個
Check this out.
哦 來了
Whoa,man.
超贊 是啊
That's pretty wicked. Yeah.
嘿 過來看看這個
Hey,come look at this.
你說什麼?
What did you just say?
他怎麼了?
What's his problem?
這傢伙想站起來
Our boy's tryin' to get up.
求求你 別傷害他! 求你了
Please,don't hurt him! Please.
我們出去吧
I say we go out.
你們為什麼要這麼做? 為什麼?
Why are you doing this? Why?
為什麼不呢?
Why not?
拍到了嗎? 拍到了
Did you get that? I got it.
她?
You think?
別人會看見的
People might see.
那又怎樣?
So?
我先上
I go first.
這是你的車? 是啊
This your car? Yeah.
不錯嘛
It's nice.
我只是來接我女朋友
Look,i'm just picking up my girlfriend.
你幹嘛!
What the hell,man!
沒人看見什麼嗎?
Did anybody see anything?
停車場中央可是該死的盲區
It's in the middle of the damn parking lot.
保安錄像呢? 只有門口才有
What about the security cam? It's only on the door.
那位女士是誰? 經理
Who's the lady over there? Manager.
她開門做早餐生意的時候發現了屍體
She discovered the bodies when she came by to open up for the breakfast crowd.
我去和她談談 知道受害人是誰嗎?
I'll go talk to her. Any idea who the victims are?
從駕照來看 一個是這兒的女服務生
Judging by the driver's license, one of them's a waitress here.
叫Jessica Miller 另一個可能是Doug Taylor
It says jessica miller, and the other one's probably doug taylor.
你不能確定?
You can't tell for sure?
老實說 光看是根本看不出來的
Honestly,you can't make an i.d.by looking at them.
Hotch
Hotch.
我停車的時候 一開始根本沒看出來是什麼
I didn't even know what it was at first when I pulled up.
他們膽子更大了 在公共場所殺人
They're definitely getting bolder. These kills were in public.
如果前幾起是象徵什麼的話 這起絕對不是了
If this is supposed to be about symbolism,it's not anymore.
這是家工薪階層的餐廳 受害人是服務生
This is a blue collar restaurant, the victim is a waitress.
沒有特殊意識 就是暴行和力量
There's no ideology behind this. It's about violence and power.
他們殺完人之後還坐在這喝啤酒
They actually sat here and drank beer after the murders.
他們在說他們不在乎
They're telling us that they don't care.
他們像一群外來逃犯
They're like those outlaws that ride into town
告訴你唯一讓他們停下來的方法 就是殺了他們
and let you know the only way to stop them is by killing them.
如果這就是他們想要的 這有一大群警察願意幫忙
If that's what they want, I know plenty of cops who'd be happy to oblige.
警探 我們要保持冷靜 什麼意思?
Detective,we need to keep our heads. Meaning what?
這個程度的恐怖行為 這種隨意性 會產生相應的影響
Meaning that this level of nihilism, this randomness, it can have a mirror impact.
你在警告我別去報仇嗎?
Are you warning me not to go after some kind of revenge?
我只是說這種程度的暴虐行為像是 不明嫌犯發出的挑戰
All i'm saying is this level of brutality is almost like a challenge from the unsubs,
想把所有人都變得和他們一樣
trying to drag everyone down to their level.
這是自然反應
And it's a natural reaction.
我只是在做我的工作
I'm just doing my job.
先回去 可以側寫了
Let's head back. We've got our profile.
有多嚴重? 非常嚴重
How bad? Bad bad.
有人在等你
You have company.
Barnes女士
Ms.barnes.
抱歉我就這麼來了
Sorry for just showing up like this.
我聽到新聞說還有受害人  不知道去哪能得到更多信息
I heard on the news that there were more victims and I didn't know where else to get answers.
這邊請
Please.
謝謝
Thank you.
是真的嗎? 是殺William的那些人幹的?
So is it true? Was it the same people who killed william?
是
Yes.
有嫌疑人了嗎?
Do you have any suspects?
沒有 但是我們已經有了嫌犯側寫
No,but we do have a profile of who these men might be.
兩位探員正告訴警方
Two of our agents are giving it to the police right now
然後在所有的新聞渠道上發佈
and we're getting it to all the news outlets.
你能解釋一下嗎? 拜託
Can you explain it to me? Please.
基本上 這些人已經失去了所有
Basically,these men are completely disenfranchised.
他們覺得活著沒有意義
They feel like they have nothing to live for.
所以尋求人或東西來歸咎責任
And they're looking for anyone or anything to blame.
外界很憤怒 時間很緊
There's a lot of anger out there. Times are tough.
但就算這樣 兇手還是沒有蹤跡
But even so,these men will stand out.
他們想挑起衝突
They'll look to provoke confrontation.
任何原因 都會被他們利用
Any excuse,they'll take it.
他們不偷受害者的東西 不對女人進行性侵害
They don't steal from their victims. They don't sexually assault the women.
他們是為了暴行而暴行
This is about violence for violence's sake.
這好像能傳染 是很怪
It's almost contagious. It's twisted.
但確實有自己傳播的動力
But it's got its own momentum.
我們需要做的是查出為什麼這些人 會走到一起
What we need to do is figure out how these men came together.
我們確定 他們和華盛頓東南部的打砸搶有關
We feel certain that they have some connection to southeast d.c.
沒人發現他們去
They go unnoticed.
現場外面也沒人看見他們
They don't seem out of place.
現場沒有指紋 不明嫌犯應該帶了手套
We have no prints from the crime scenes, so we believe that the unsubs wear gloves.
DNA測試需要幾周時間 我們沒時間
Dna testing could take weeks, and we don't have that kind of time.
東南地區大部分都是黑人  但如果不明嫌犯在這堣u作
The majority of the population of southeast is black, but if the unsubs work in this area,
他們可以是任何人種
they could be any race.
考慮到死者的身形
Because of the physical nature of the murders
以及不明嫌犯能同時控制的受害者人數
and the amount of control these unsubs exert over their victims,
我們相信他們身材高大 至少身體強壯
we believe that these unsubs are large or at least extremely physically fit.
而且喜歡集體行動
And they have a pack mentality.
徹底搜查當地酒吧和餐廳
Canvass the local bars and restaurants.
看是否有一群人符合描述
See if there's a group of men who fit this description.
他們可能很關注新聞
And these men will be obsessed with the media coverage.
任何能再現他們犯罪的情況
Any chance to relive their crimes.
所以監視以往的犯罪現場 很有可能他們會回去
So stake out the past crime scenes. There's a good chance that they'll revisit them.
他們很可能有前科 家庭破裂 或進過少管所
They most likely come from troubled backgrounds, broken homes, youth detention centers.
可能是因為憤怒聚在一起的
They probably bonded over their anger.
現在看來他們成為一個整體了
And now it's like they've become one person.
這就是他們的統一性
It's their whole identity.
這些人覺得自己是一幫匪徒
See,these guys, they think of themselves as some type of gangsters,
社會規則對他們不適用
like society's rules don't apply to them.
他們覺得暴行能得到力量和尊重
They equate violence with power and respect.
也能得到自我尊重
And that goes for selfrespect as well.
他們怎麼可能毫無緣由地 殘殺無辜的人?
What could they possibly get out of killing innocent people for no reason?
這種人和我們不同  他們對別人沒感情
People like this, they're not like you and me. They don't feel empathy.
某種程度上 他們只有在製造恐懼和混亂時 才覺得自己活著
In a way,they only feel alive when they're creating fear and chaos.
靠這些側寫 警察能抓到這些人嗎?
And your profiles,they help catch these people?
會的
They do.
謝謝你幫我熬過這些
Thank you for helping me through this.
我應該的
Of course.
警探
Detective.
我想說 在現場時 我不是想要責怪你不專業
I just wanted to say that at the crime scene it was not my intention to accuse you of being unprofessional.
是嗎?
Yeah?
只是我知道這種案子會讓你質疑人性
It's just that I know what it's like to work a case that makes you question humanity,
所以提醒你克服這些影響並不是最壞的
and it's not the worst thing to remind yourself to rise above it a little,
否則我們會失去自我
or we lose ourselves.
很感謝你告訴他們側寫
I appreciate you giving the men the profile.
杜邦的復仇!
Rage In Dupont!
噢 不
Oh,no.
杜邦區Thompkins廣場將有暴動
我有發現
Sir,i've got something.
我查了社交網站 看不明嫌犯有沒有用電腦交流
I've been monitoring social networking sites to see if the unsubs communicate electronically.
對
Right.
有一條信息跳出來了 我發到你手機了
There's a text that's blowing up. I sent it to your phone.
點擊率已經超過一千
There's over a thousand hits already.
是一個破壞杜邦區附近車和餐廳的計劃
It's a plan to vandalize cars and restaurants around dupont circle.
信息說什麼時候發生?
When does the text say this is supposed to happen?
今晚9點
Tonight,9:00.
杜邦區不在嫌犯慣常活動區
Dupont circle's not in the unsubs' usual comfort zone.
不明嫌犯也不像是劃分了勢力範圍
And it's not like these unsubs to share control.
Andrews警探 我是Hotchner探員
Detective andrews, this is agent hotchner.
我們收到一條警報 已經發給你了
I just sent you a text to which we've been alerted.
好 當然 我們馬上到
Right. Absolutely. We're on our way.
不離開的人一律拘捕
You will be arrested if you do not disperse.
每個入口處都有貨車
We got wagons at every entry point.
他們盡快裝完 我就能把他們抓住
They're filling them up faster than I can bring them to holding.
發生什麼事?
What happened?
我的人去抓人 他們反抗 我叫了增援
My men went to make arrests, people started resisting, I called for reinforcements.
知道誰是煽動者嗎?
Do you know who the instigators are?
不知道任何跡象和原因
There's no rhyme or reason I can tell.
沒收手機
Confiscate the cell phones.
找到信息來源 就能抓到元兇
When we get to the origins of the text message, you'll have your ringleaders.
還在通知家人 審訊大部分鬧事者
They're still notifying families and processing most of the rioters.
Garcia查到什麼了嗎?
Did garcia come up with anything?
有 她已經找到了最早收到信息的兩台手機
Yeah. She was able to isolate the first 2 cell phones in the chain.
警探 我們認為不明嫌犯不在其中
Detective,we don't think our unsubs are in there,
但還是想審訊有可能的元兇
but we'd still like to interrogate the possible ringleaders.
我不認為
I don't think so.
但我們需要徹底排除嫌疑
But we need to eliminate them absolutely as suspects.
我們自己可以處理
We can handle it on our own.
我們不是說你們不行
We're not saying you can't.
有問題嗎?
Is there a problem?
你讓我的人徹底搜查酒吧找成年人
You guys had my men out there canvassing bars looking for adults
我們本來可以查查流氓和少年犯罪記錄
when I could have been doing gang sweeps,going through juvenile records.
那是在浪費時間
That would have been a waste of your time.
你們沒注意吧 外面的那些都是孩子
In case you hadn't noticed, those are kids out there.
我們認為昨晚的暴亂與謀殺無關
We don't believe last night's riot is connected to the murders.
怎麼可能沒關係?
How could it not be?
因為我們要找的不明嫌犯年紀更大
Because the unsubs we're looking for are older.
他們只在華盛頓東南地區犯事
They operate entirely out of southeast d.c.
他們對受害人採取絕對控制 暴力行為非常有針對性
They exercise extreme control over their victims, and violence is up close and personal.
昨晚的事都不符合側寫
None of what happened here last night fits the profile.
別再說側寫了 我可能損失了一百萬
Enough with the profile. I got probably a million dollars worth of damage.
兩名警員受傷了
I got two cops injured.
可能會因為警察反應過度變得更糟
Which was probably made worse by police overreaction.
什麼意思? 我警告過你
Meaning what? I warned you.
這種案子會讓人更情緒化
Cases like this, people get too emotional.
在我的部門 你們都是客人
You're here as a guest of my department.
我們只是想幫忙
We're only trying to help.
如果你們確定這些孩子都不是兇手 為什麼還要審訊他們?
If you're so sure none of those kids are the killers, why bother interrogating them at all?
因為我們要確定
Because we need to be certain.
如果我們是對的  如果這只是孩子們的挑釁行為
If we're right, if this is just some sort of teenage dare,
我保證 不明嫌犯會很快做出反應
I guarantee you that the unsubs are going to respond very quickly.
真謝謝你看透了這些  但之後我們想自己接手了
I appreciate your insight, but we'd like to take things from here on our own.
謝謝你們所做的一切
Thank you for everything you've done.
你們可以從這兩個人開始問
You're gonna want to start with these 2 names.
你幫不了我 我想和負責的警官說
You're not helping. I want to speak to the officer in charge.
Barnes女士
Ms.barnes.
我想知道發生什麼事了
I need someone to tell me what's going on.
我們正在查
We're trying to figure it out.
是他們殺了William嗎?
Are those the ones who killed william?
不是他們 但是他們引起暴動
No,they're not. But they started the riot.
他們只是一群傻孩子
They're just a bunch of stupid kids.
對 打砸搶 隨意襲擊路人的 不正是他們嗎
Yeah,who vandalize and attack people at random.
我說過 這樣的事情都有內部力量
I told you these things have their own momentum.
你確定嗎? 我很抱歉
Are you sure? I'm sorry.
都玩開心了嗎? 都出人命了 你們不管嗎?
So did you all have fun,huh? Do you even care that someone died?
Barnes女士 你需要冷靜
Ms.barnes,you really need to calm down.
不 沒人在乎 不是這樣的
No,no one cares. That's not true.
沒人在乎 有人死了 難道這只是遊戲嗎 只是工作嗎? 過後就忘?
No one cares. Someone dies and it's all just a game or a job and everyone just moves on.
不是的 人們在乎 我也在乎
That's not true. People do care,and I care.
他們毫無緣由地殺了我哥哥
They killed my brother for no reason!
拜託 我送你出去 呼吸下新鮮空氣.
Please. Let me walk you outside and get you some air. Please.
跟我走 沒事的
Walk with me. It's ok.
沒事的
It's all right.
我進入了你指定區域警報服務台
I've logged into police dispatch for the area you've isolated.
如果有人報案的話 我們能馬上知道
If anything's reported, we'll know when they know.
等等 我們還在做這個案子?
Wait,are we staying on the case?
我們知道不明嫌犯會對昨晚的暴動有所反應
We all know that these unsubs are gonna react to last night's riot.
但是Emily說的對 他們叫我們別管了
But emily's right. They asked us to step aside.
Andrews是個好警察 只是現在太情緒化了
Andrews is a good cop. He's just too emotional right now.
不管他同不同意 如果我們不跟進  他和我們都會後悔的
If we don't stay on,with or without his permission, he and all the rest of us will regret it.
Morgan呢?
Where's morgan?
他和Barnes女士在一起
Uh,he's with ms. Barnes.
你確定你沒事嗎?
You sure you're gonna be all right?
我沒瘋 真的
You know,i'm not crazy, really.
Tamara 你遭受了巨大的打擊 又想早日得到真相
Tamara,you've been through a trauma, and you're processing a lot.
所以有點失常是正常的
It's normal to lose it a little.
謝謝 你所做的一切
Thank you. For everything.
我只是在做我的工作 不 你..
I'm just doing my job. No,you're...
你是好人
You're a good person.
那這會怎麼結束呢?
So how's this gonna end?
什麼?
What?
調查 我是說 會發生什麼呢?
The investigation. I mean,what happens?
如果一定要猜 昨晚的暴動 不明嫌犯不會高興的
Well,if I had to guess, last night's riotsour unsubs aren't gonna like it.
這是他們一致性
This is their whole identity.
他們不喜歡被人搶風頭
They're not gonna like sharing the attention.
那麼又有人要喪命了
So more people are gonna die.
他們只在那個地區殺人 我們的側寫很可靠
They're killing in a small area. Our profile is solid.
會有人認出他們
Somebody will recognize them.
你知道沒那麼容易的
You don't think it's gonna be that easy.
我真的要回去了
I really need to get back to my team.
對 抱歉 謝謝你... 送我回來
Yeah. I'm sorry. Thank you for,uh, driving me home.
不用謝
You're welcome.
Morgan探員
Agent morgan.
你認為能抓到他們嗎?
Do you think you can get these guys?
我們正在接近他們
We're closing in.
他們一定感受到了
And they're bound to start feeling it.
這些人 當他們發現有追兵了 就很有可能借警方之手自殺
See,guys like this, when they feel trapped, they most likely commit suicide by cop.
好
Good.
他媽的你們想去哪?
Where the hell do you think you're going?
我和社區巡警談過
I talked to the beat cops.
他們已通知當地經營場所留意
They're getting word out to local businesses to keep an eye out for anyone
那些對昨晚暴動情緒激動的人
who seems agitated by the news of last night's riot.
現在Andrews肯定知道那些孩子 不是不明嫌犯了
By now,andrews has to know that none of those kids are the unsubs.
他一定會加強東南區的警力
Then he's bound to beef up police presence in the southeast.
我們也應該去
We should be there,too.
我們反應越迅速越有利
The faster we can react, the more we can help.
你覺得不明嫌犯知道暴動了嗎?
Do you think the unsubs know about the riot?
頭版新聞 沒理由看不到
Front page news. I don't know how they can't.
如果側寫正確呢?
And if the profile's right?
他們會迅速反擊 而且手段殘暴
Their reaction's gonna be quick and it's gonna be brutal.
基本上是說 知道要閃電了
Basically,it's like knowing that lightning is gonna strike
卻不知道會擊中哪
but not being able to pinpoint where.
3杯
3 drafts.
抱歉 你不能把這個帶進來
I'm sorry,you can't have that in here.
什麼? 這個?
What? This?
這是責任問題 避免別人受傷
It's a liability issue, that's all, in case somebody gets hurt.
沒問題
No problem.
能談談麼? 可以 怎麼回事?
Can we have a talk? Yeah. What's up?
呃 我首先要說我愛你
Uh,first I would like to say that I love you,
我... 我...我愛你 正是因為你很關心別人...
and iithe thing I love the most about you is how much you care about people
Garcia 幹嘛? 怎麼回事?
garcia,what?What's going on?
我覺得你應該和Tamara Barnes切斷聯繫
I think you need to cut contact with tamara barnes.
我沒有和她聯繫 她當時就在警察局
I didn't make contact with her. She was at the police station.
好吧 看著我的眼睛 告訴我這個案子 最近有突破的時候 你不是直奔向她
Yeah,ok,look me in the eye and tell me that the first break in this case you don't run right to her
親自告訴她消息
and give her the news yourself.
Penelope 她失去了兄弟 她只想知道答案
Penelope,she lost her brother. She just wants answers.
明白了 那我自願去安慰這些家庭
I get it. I volunteer counseling these families.
我知道她需要熬過什麼
I know what she's going through.
那這又是唱的哪出戲?
Then where is this coming from?
好吧 我們就拋開道德不談 因為那一說就長篇大論了
Ok,let's just ignore the whole ethical dilemma, 'cause that's just too,too big.
如果你要為此案作證
And if you were to testify on this case,
若有人找出你和受害者家人有牽扯
the whole thing would unravel if anyone were to find out that
整個事情都會敗露 喔哦 停下
you're involved with a member of the victim's family. Whoa,stop.
你知道我愛你 也尊重你
I love you, and I respect you. You know that.
但現在你太過分了
But right now you're way out of bounds.
我沒有牽扯進去
I'm not involved.
整個小組都在這媬鴟 而你卻和她在一起
The team is here working on a case, and you're with her.
你牽扯進去了
You're involved.
告訴你吧 她在車站迷路  所以我開車送她回家
For your information, she lost it back at the station, so I drove her home.
句號 但對她來說不是
End of story. But not for her.
Derek 她很悲傷 很煩惱 很憤怒
Derek, she's so sad and so confused and angry
正四處尋求別人的懷抱 讓事情好轉
and desperately looking for anyone to swoop in and make it all better,
除非你一直待在她的身邊  伴她度過悲傷的每個階段
and unless you're all in and can be there for every stage of the grieving process,
否則你是她對這個世界 不信任的又一因素
you're just another reason for her to not trust the world.
她只是想知道為什麼而已
She's simply trying to understand why this happened.
並沒有為什麼 她只會拚命去找尋理由
There is no why, and she'll make herself crazy trying to find one.
別說是...
Don't tell me.
東南區的酒吧 兩人死亡 他們在等你
Bar in southeast,2 dead. They're waiting for you.
我得走了 是的
I got to go. Yeah.
你在這媟F什麼?
What are you doing here?
警探們 我們可以遲點再談此事
Detective,we can argue about this later.
現在此處是犯罪現場 我們是來幫忙的
Right now you have a crime scene and we're here to help.
他們先把酒保的雙手釘在吧檯上
They nailed the bartender's hands to the bar first.
其他人更容易逃跑
Other bastard got off easier.
他們赤手毆打他
They just plain beat him.
真煩死了 我們明明是對的 卻不起作用
I'm getting real sick of us being right and it just not mattering.
怪了 什麼?
This is weird. What?
不明嫌犯身體很強壯
The unsubs are extremely physical.
他們用鈍物無情地毆打受害者
They beat their victims mercilessly with blunt objects.
為什麼這些釘子沒有釘到底?
Why aren't these nails pounded in?
可能用的是釘槍
Probably used a nail gun.
隨著社區的翻新和新房的售出
With all the gentrification and turnover in housing in the neighborhood,
最近什麼最常見?
what's a common sight these days?
施工人員 承包商 建築工人
Builders, contractors,and construction workers.
顯而易見
We wouldn't give it a second thought.
等等
Wait a minute.
第一起 入室殺害4人 我一直想不明白
Killing 4 people in that first home invasionthat never made sense to me.
不明嫌犯需要進化過程
Unsubs build to something like that.
如果那不是他們第一次謀殺呢?
What if this wasn't their first murder?
先是幾起故意破壞 有代表性的破壞
The first two rounds of vandalism, they were typical.
砸車窗 砸飯店的玻璃
Car windows smashed, restaurants with the plate glass broken.
但是最後一起 就在入室之前 是隨意挑選的工地
But that last case, right before the home invasion, that was a random construction site.
獨戶住宅
A singlefamily townhouse.
Prentiss 你自己找出的 是的
Prentiss,you flagged it yourself. Yeah,yeah.
嘿 Garcia
Hey,garcia.
我要那戶被洗劫的公寓地址
I need the address on that townhouse that was vandalized.
我不明白 我們能怎麼幫忙
I don't understand how we can help.
先生 我們相信破壞你們房子的人 就是製造這區域謀殺案的人
Sir,we believe that whoever vandalized your house is responsible for the murders in the area.
噢 我知道 我們在報紙上讀到過
Oh,i know. We've read the papers.
但老實說 我們不想再提及此事
But,honestly,that's not something we're gonna think about right now.
我們還認為  你的房子遭到破壞是有原因的
We also think it's possible that your home was vandalized for a reason.
什麼意思?
What do you mean?
我們能進來麼?
May we?
可以 請進 謝謝
Yes,please. Thank you.
我們相信在警方發現第一起謀殺案之前 還有另外一宗謀殺案
We believe there may have been another murder before the first one the police became aware of.
你們認為有屍體藏在這  在我們的房子?
You think there might be a body hidden here, on our property?
有可能 至少我們要找的人 可能在這堣u作過
It's possible. At the very least, the men we're looking for may have worked here.
噢 天哪
Oh,my god.
在施工期間 工人們有沒有吵架?
Were there any issues with workers during construction?
不 沒有 有誰過度反抗嗎?
No,nothing. Did anyone appear overly confrontational?
我只和承包商聯繫 他為人友善
I just had contact with our contractor, and he was friendly.
我明白 施工期間 人來人往
I understand people come and go during construction,
但你們有注意到誰突然消失了嗎?
but was there anyone at all that you may have noticed suddenly wasn't around?
噢 不 什麼事?
Oh,no. What is it?
我提到的承包商...
The contractor I mentioned...
房子造到破壞後 我打電話叫他維修
After the vandalism, we called him to oversee the repairs.
他一直沒回電話
He never called us back.
警方報告上稱 所有房間都被砸壞 唯獨一間倖免
The police report said that every room in the house was destroyed except one.
是的 除了嬰兒房 其他都被砸 他們沒碰那房間
Yeah,they smashed every room except the nursery. That one they didn't touch.
我們得看看
We need to see it.
這牆是撐大梁的
This wall is structural.
如果不是因為非常重要 我不會如此請求
I wouldn't ask you this unless I felt it was incredibly important.
我需要打開這面牆 不行
I need to open up this wall. No.
如果不知道真相 我們怎麼能住得下去
We can't live here and not know.
女士 我發誓 即使要我親手動手
Ma'am, I promise you,even if I have to do every bit of the work myself,
都會將這面牆修好 和之前的一模一樣
this wall will be repaired and it'll go right back to being exactly what you want.
求你了? 好吧
Please? Ok.
我是FBI的Emily Prentiss探員
This is agent emily prentiss with the fbi.
請派個SCSI小組過來
I need an scsi unit.
發現屍體
We've got a body.
待不下去了
I can't be here.
我們借一步說話
Let's move over here.
你們有地方落腳嗎?
Is there someplace the two of you can stay?
是的 我可以打電話給朋友
Yes. We have friends I can call.
警方給你們錄完口供後  會送你們去朋友家
After you give the police a statement, they can take you to your friends' house.
謝謝
Thank you.
覺得他們能挺得過嗎?
You think they'll be ok?
不知道呀 你看  重新裝修了你的夢想家園
I don't know.I mean,you redo your dream home,
準備開始全新的生活 然後發生這個?
about to start a new chapter of your life, and then this?
你怎麼知道的?
How did you know?
其他的犯罪現場都很殘暴 但在控制之下
The other crime scenes were brutal. But it also had control.
他們不慌不忙 這種手法 肯定是入室謀殺之前練就的
They took their time, that type of m.o.had to start before the home invasions.
整個房子都被搗毀 除了這間 為什麼?
This entire place was destroyed except this room. Why?
因為他們埋了承包商後 花時間重建了這面牆
Because they took the time to rebuild the wall once they buried the contractor.
完全正確
Exactly.
如果他們砸毀這房子 會被人發現
If they smashed this place up, he could have been discovered.
但是 把屍體整到牆?
But still,a body inside the wall?
這像是施工人員的傳統
It's like a builders tradition.
留下點東西 當做給後來者的信息
You leave a little something behind to send a message to the people who may do work down the road.
報紙頭條
Front page of a newspaper.
施工隊的照片
A photo of the construction crew.
像個時間膠囊 好吧
It's like a time capsule. Ok.
那麼你需要什麼來重建這面牆?
Ok,so what would you need to rebuild this wall?
牆板 磚塊 電線?
Drywall,brickwork, electrical?
我給Garcia打電話
I'm gonna call garcia.
嘿 美女
Hey,girl.
我們還好吧? 是的 我們還好
Are we good? Yeah,we're good.
好吧 你需要什麼?
Ok. What do you need?
把被搗毀公寓的地址找出來 找到
Ok,pull up the address of the townhouse that was vandalized. Got it.
找到承包商的工作許可證
Ok. Give me work permits for the contractor.
那位是...James Morris  他就是不明嫌犯?
That would be... James morris. Is he our unsub?
不 事實上 恐怕他是第一位受害者
No,actually,i'm afraid he's our first victim.
上面有Morris的轉包商嗎? 嗯 有
Does it list morris' subcontractors? Yes,it does.
很好 我需要被雇來做電活
All right,i need all the names and addresses for whoever
砌磚和牆板的人名及地址
was hired to do the electrical, brickwork,and drywall.
那就有3個名字 1個地址
That would be 3 names,one address.
他們真住一起 是的
So they do live together. Yeah.
Anacostia附近 B大街5058號 詳細地址發給你...就現在
5058 b street near anacostia, particulars coming to you... Now.
謝謝 寶貝
Thanks,babe.
我們是對的 果然是一夥
We were right. They're a pack.
我們先進去 你們的案子
We go in first. It's your case.
警察! FBI!
Police! Fbi!
把他按住!
Get him down!
另外2個在哪?
Where are the other two?
你耍我 對吧? Dave
You gotta be kidding me, right? Dave.
喜歡看不 長官?
You like that,sir?
我還有很多
I got more.
另外2個在哪?
Where are the others?
去死
Go to hell.
Garcia 我要所有住戶的車輛信息
Garcia,i need vehicle information on all the residents.
拉他起來
Get him up.
收到
Got it.
全境通緝 廂式貨車  華盛頓車牌74DA4
Apbstation wagon, d.c.plate 74deltaalpha4.
再查他們目前是否有登記其他工作
I also need to know if they're registered on any jobs right now.
8號大街南門看到廂式貨車 往哈弗大街行駛 東南方向
I got a visual on the station wagon just south of 8th, heading toward half street,southeast.
就在他們現在工地旁邊
That's right next to their current work site.
知道我為什麼不爽嗎?
You know what gets me?
我們知道你們窮困潦倒 憤世嫉俗
See,we figured you were down and out,pissed off.
但你們還是有工作的啊
But you're out here working.
這是遇到什麼天大的挫折了 非要拿他人來出氣?
What is so godawful about your life that you gotta take it out on the rest of the world?
好玩啊 老大
It was fun,boss.
東南區 哈弗大街922號 部署作戰小組 謝謝
Deploy tactical units 922 half street,southeast. Thanks.
找到他們了
We got 'em.
別管他 Morgan 他什麼都不是 我們走
Forget him,morgan. He's nothing. Let's go.
有幾個?
How many we got?
25個 可能30
25,maybe 30.
我們不能不做
That ought to do it.
我安排了狙擊手在高處就位  一組人包抄後面
I got snipers up high, I got a team around back.
一旦確認堶惆S有人質 我就下令進攻
Once we're sure there's not a hostage inside, i'll give the order to breach.
你要走了?
You leaving?
你已經控制局面了
You've got this under control.
他就這麼走開了?
Is he just gonna walk away?
看樣子是的
Looks like it.
我還以為他已經掌控了這場遊戲呢
Just when I thought he was back on top of his game.
這邊至少有12位警察 都想為百姓報仇
You got at least 2 dozen cops, all looking for revenge.
堶惘2個精神病 準備獻上壓軸大戲
You got two psychopaths inside, ready to play out their fantasy end.
你想也打上一槍的話...打吧
You want to take your shot... Take it.
我們的工作完成了
Our job is done.
到時間了? 真TMD
Is it time? What the hell,right?
保持鎮定 把這玩意當槍一樣握在前面
Just keep your head up and you hold this son of a bitch out front like it's a gun.
有槍!
Gun!
莎士比亞曾寫道 "狂暴的快樂 都有狂暴的結局"
William shakespeare wrote, "these violent delights have violent ends."
我想來告訴你 案子結了
I just wanted to come by and let you know that it was over.
我們抓到他們了
We got 'em.
犯罪心理 第五季 第04集 絕望
== 結束 ==
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode04 Hopeless